
//client questions
export const clientQuestions =  {
    general:[
    {
        question:"Is Curant24 an intermediary?",
        answer: "Curant24 is more than just a mediator between organizations / companies and freelancers. We offer: \n - an extensive international and national online platform where we bring supply and demand together.\n - We take over the total administration of both parties\n - An online system (your Curant24 account) where all documents can be found such as contracts, time sheets, invoices, receipts\n"
    },{
        question:"What is Curant24?",
        answer: "Curant24 is a platform where freelancers and clients from every conceivable industry do business with each other.\n Clients have the option to search for freelancers for free in our extensive database for their assignment. Or can immediately call on the help of Curant24. And vice versa, freelancers can search for the most current assignments on Curant24 \n Curant 24 was founded in 2009 and has offices in various countries worldwide. Curant24 is an intermediary agency that brings freelancers from every industry together with clients.\n Curant24 is part of NatureTower bv with more than 100 employees worldwide."
    },{
        question:"How did Curant24 originate?",
        answer:"Curant 24 was founded in 2009 and has offices in various countries worldwide. Curant24 is an intermediary agency that brings freelancers from every industry together with clients.\n  Curant24 is part of NatureTower bv with more than 100 employees worldwide.\n"
    },{
        question:"How does Curant24 work for the freelancer?",
        answer:"On Curant24 you will find various assignments for you as a freelancer. From plumber to childcare. First you create a Curant24 account and then you view the available assignments. Is there anything interesting in there? Then click on 'I am interested' and let the client know that you are interested.\nIs the client also interested in your services?\nThen we discuss all the conditions of the assignment together with the client. So that there are no surprises for both parties. If everything has been properly discussed and both parties agree to the terms and conditions.\nThen Curant24 does the rest and we arrange all administration between both parties.\nYou only need to submit your work hours weekly in your Curant24 account. Your invoice is automatically generated from the system every Tuesday and sent to the client.\nThis is all neatly stored in your account.\nAnd you can choose when you have the invoices paid, 7, 14 or 30 days\n"
    },{
        question:"How does Curant24 work for the client?",
        answer:"On Curant24 you will find various freelancers from plumbers to childcare for your assignments. In just a few clicks you can create an account and post a assignment. You can invite suitable freelancers or freelancers themselves show interest in your assignment.\n Have you found the right freelancer and is the freelancer also interested in your assignment?\n Then we discuss all the conditions of the assignment together with the freelancer. So that there are no surprises for both parties. If everything has been properly discussed and both parties agree to the terms and conditions. Then only the contracts are signed\nThen Curant24 does the rest and we arrange all administration between both parties.\nYou will receive the invoices neatly in your Curant24 account every week. In your account you will also find all contracts between you and the freelancers, invoices, working hours of the freelancers, and any receipts."
    },{
        question:"How do I create a Curant24 account (profile)?",
        answer:"You can sign up for free and without obligation via the www.Curant24.nl platform, via this link"
    },{
        question:"Why freelancers choose Curant24",
        answer:"Curant24 is specialized internationally and nationally and is active in every industry. Thanks to our broad knowledge of the profession, we know better than anyone else what each industry looks like and what the possibilities are.\nBecause of the good cooperation with clients over the years who use our platform to place their assignments. Can we offer you as freelancers a valuable offer?\n"
    },{
        question:"What makes Curant24 different from other agencies.",
        answer:"Various consultants work at Curant24, all of whom have knowledge of their industry. Thanks to our experience, knowledge and close cooperation with companies, organizations and freelancers, we know what is needed within a company or organization to successfully complete a assignment.\n We strive to take a assignment to a higher level by not only looking at the required qualities of the freelancer. But we also look at the person, does the freelancer fit in with the organization or company? We know from experience that a match on paper is not always a match."
    },{
        question:"Why do clients choose Curant24",
        answer:"Most clients like to keep their focus on the core business. It takes time to find a suitable freelancer. That is why clients have been using us since 2009. We are specialists in mediating the right freelancers with clients.\nClients also have the option to search for a freelancer free of charge via our extensive database of freelancers. The advantage of this is that it is clearly indicated which freelancers are immediately available. And we only have qualified and screened freelancers in our database.\nIf a assignment has to be carried out abroad, we also have Curant24 branches that are active abroad. Who could be looking for a freelancer internationally.\n"
    },{
        question:"What does Curant24 do with my personal and company data",
        answer:"View and download the privacy statement here"
    },{
        question:"What about the responsibility in case of incidents during the assignments?",
        answer:"Curant24 is only the mediator and is not liable in the event of incidents during assignments. The freelancer is insured for accidents/incidents during work.\nWithout business liability insurance, the freelancers are not allowed to work via Curant24"
    },{
        question:"I am unable to upload my documents to my profile.",
        answer:"You can only upload your documents as PDF. \n Below is a link to convert your documents into PDF format, if necessary: \n https://www.google.com/search?client=firefox-b-d&q=jpg+convert+to+pdf"
    }   
    ],
    cancellations:[
        {
            question:"The freelancer is already on location and working, but I will no longer need the freelancer. Can I still shorten the service?",
            answer:"When a service has started, a change is limited. \n A shift for a day, for example 8 or 9 hours, can be shortened by 1 hour in case of redundancy. The reason for this is that the Tadaah has reserved this day for work and an agreement has been made for this. \n Afternoon or morning shifts, for example BSO (out-of-school care), cannot be shortened"
        },{
            question:"Can I cancel a freelancer if a freelancer is already scheduled?",
            answer:"The assignment agreement states that a service can always be canceled free of charge up to 24 hours before the start.\n A cancellation within 24 hours before the start is also possible, but the contractor will then receive a compensation of € 100,= for lost income, only if it cannot receive a replacement order for the day in question."
        },{
            question:"The freelancer is redundant and has indicated that he will not complete the scheduled service in full. How can we still adjust the service?",
            answer:"If the freelancer and the organization or company have jointly agreed to adjust / shorten the planned service after the start, this change must be recorded in writing. \n An assignment agreement has been entered into and this can only be changed if both parties agree. A change must be communicated to info@curant24"
        },{
            question:"I have an assignment agreement with a freelancer that I want to change, is that possible?",
            answer:"Yes that is possible, the terms and conditions and the assignment agreement state that a client, in all reasonableness, requires a freelancer to carry out the assignment at a different location. \n The following must be taken into account: if the client wishes such a change, the associated costs (travel costs, parking costs and travel time) will be borne by the client. After all, it is the client who wants the change. For example, a freelancer is hired at a location with free parking for a 9am-5pm shift. The client wants this person to go to another location where parking has been paid, then the costs of parking are for the client. \n The costs for traveling there and the travel time (in accordance with the hourly rate) are also for the account of the client. If the freelancer uses the car, it is reasonable to charge € 0.19 per kilometer. If public transport is used, the travel costs can easily be determined using the OV chip card or the travel costs according to the website 9292.nl"
        },{
            question:"A situation has arisen where the use of the freelancer is no longer necessary, what are the options?",
            answer:"That depends on whether the service has already started. A service has commenced after the expiry of the date and time as stated in the assignment agreement. \n The assignment can then no longer be withdrawn, it is possible to shorten the assignment by a maximum of 1 hour, an assignment of 9 hours can be shortened to 8 hours. This may, for example, be used in the event of redundancy or any other circumstance as a result of which the client is forced to close a assignment, including corona-related measures. \n The assignment can be canceled up to 24 hours before the start of the service, in which case the client owes the contractor a fee of € 100. If the assignment is canceled earlier, so before 24 hours before the start, there are no costs involved."
        },{
            question:"As a client, can you cancel an order within 24 hours?",
            answer:"When a client cancels a service within 24 hours, the freelancer receives compensation. The compensation of €100 is compensation for canceling within 24 hours and there is no work in return. \n The freelancer does not have to come to the location. The freelancer can take on another service. \n This cancellation is not possible if the freelancer is already at the location and has therefore already started the assignment."
        },{
            question:"As a client, can you shorten a service within 24 hours?",
            answer:"If an agreement has commenced, i.e. after the expiry of the date and time stated in this agreement, it can no longer be changed, unless the parties agree otherwise. \n However, it is possible to shorten an agreement of at least 8 hours by 1 hour to an agreement of 7 hours, for example in the event of redundancy by the contractor. Assignments shorter than 4 hours cannot be changed, unless the parties agree otherwise."
        }
    ],
    howToPlaceAssignment:[
        {
            question:"How do I post an assignment on Curant24",
            answer:"Explain clearly"
        },{
            question:"When can a project be accepted?",
            answer:"When the freelancer meets all the requirements that are asked. Watch out for money for assignments in childcare. \n An assignment can be accepted if the diploma meets the requirements. For example, there are pedagogues who are allowed to work at the BSO but not at a baby group."
        },{
            question:"What is the minimum rate for a project?",
            answer:"From January 1, 2021, the minimum rate for a freelance assignment is €16 per hour."
        },{
            question:"Can you, as a client, cancel a project within 24 hours?",
            answer:"When a client cancels a service within 24 hours, the freelancer receives compensation. The compensation of €100 is compensation for canceling within 24 hours and there is no work in return. \n The freelancer does not have to come to the location. The freelancer can take on another service. This cancellation is not possible if the freelancer is already at the location and has therefore already started the assignment."
        },{
            question:"What are reserve services",
            answer:"Reserve duty , means that the freelancer is on standby and going in place of a sick colleague. \n The freelancer receives an email as soon as a colleague calls in sick, stating which service the freelancer will take over. In this way, as a client, you are always assured that the project can go ahead."
        },{
            question:"What about the responsibility in case of incidents during the projects?",
            answer:"Curant24 is only the mediator and is not liable in the event of incidents during assignments. The freelancer is insured for accidents/incidents during work.\n Without business liability insurance, the freelancers are not allowed to work via Curant24"
        },{
            question:"Can the freelancer also accept projects directly from Curant24's clients, outside of Curant24?",
            answer:"No, this is not allowed. Clients remain customers of Curant24 at all times. Clients of Curant24 are not allowed to directly offer assignments to the freelancers and vice versa. \n This is in conflict with the General Terms and Conditions of Curant24. See our Terms and Conditions."
        }
    ],
    assignmentAgreementWithFreelancer:[
        {
            question:"I have an assignment agreement with a freelancer but he wants to be replaced, is that possible and how does this work?",
            answer:"A freelancer is not an employee and therefore different provisions apply. \n Three elements are met in an employment contract: (1) there is a relationship of authority, (2) wages are paid and (3) there is an obligation to perform the work personally. \n An assignment agreement is not an employment contract because there is no obligation to perform the work personally. It is therefore possible that a freelancer is replaced by another. However, it is only possible if the replacement meets the same objective criteria to be allowed to perform this service. \n By this we mean: having a correct VOG, a correct diploma and professional liability insurance.\n Note: For organisations/companies and freelancers active in childcare.\n It is important to take into account that the responsible employee of the organization / company ensures that the VOG is linked in the Childcare Persons Register, that the diploma is checked for authenticity and whether it is suitable for the assignment that is being carried out.\n Naturally, Curant24 helps to make the process run as smoothly as possible."
        },{
            question:"I have an assignment agreement with a freelancer that I want to change, is that possible?",
            answer:"Yes that is possible, the terms and conditions and the assignment agreement state that a client, in all reasonableness, requires a freelancer to carry out the assignment at a different location. \n The following must be taken into account: if the client wishes such a change, the associated costs (travel costs, parking costs and travel time) will be borne by the client. After all, it is the client who wants the change. For example: a Curant24 is hired at a location with free parking for a shift from 9 a.m. to 5 p.m. The client wants this person to go to another location where parking has been paid, then the costs of parking are for the client. \n The costs for traveling there and the travel time (in accordance with the hourly rate) are also for the account of the client. If Curant24 uses the car, it is reasonable to charge € 0.19 per kilometer. \n If public transport is used, the travel costs can easily be determined using the OV chip card or the travel costs according to the website 9292.nl."
        }
    ],
    invoicesPayments:[
        {
            question:"I have an assignment agreement with a freelancer but he wants to be replaced, is that possible and how does this work?",
            answer:"A freelancer is not an employee and therefore different provisions apply. Three elements are met in an employment contract: (1) there is a relationship of authority, (2) wages are paid and (3) there is an obligation to perform the work personally. \n An assignment agreement is not an employment contract because there is no obligation to perform the work personally. It is therefore possible that a freelancer is replaced by another. However, it is only possible if the replacement meets the same objective criteria to be allowed to perform this service. \n By this we mean: having a correct VOG, a correct diploma and professional liability insurance. \n Note: For organisations/companies and freelancers active in childcare. \n It is important to take into account that the responsible employee of the organization / company ensures that the VOG is linked in the Childcare Persons Register, that the diploma is checked for authenticity and whether it is suitable for the assignment that is being carried out.\n Naturally, Curant24 helps to make the process run as smoothly as possible. \n"
        },{
            question:"I have an assignment agreement with a freelancer that I want to change, is that possible?",
            answer:"Yes that is possible, the terms and conditions and the assignment agreement state that a client, in all reasonableness, requires a freelancer to carry out the assignment at a different location. \n The following must be taken into account: if the client wishes such a change, the associated costs (travel costs, parking costs and travel time) will be borne by the client. \n After all, it is the client who wants the change. For example: a Curant24 is hired at a location with free parking for a shift from 9 a.m. to 5 p.m. \n The client wants this person to go to another location where parking has been paid, then the costs of parking are for the client. \n The costs for traveling there and the travel time (in accordance with the hourly rate) are also for the account of the client.  \n If Curant24 uses the car, it is reasonable to charge € 0.19 per kilometer. If public transport is used, the travel costs can easily be determined using the OV chip card or the travel costs according to the website 9292.nl."
        }
    ],
    findFreelancer:[
        {
            question:"How can I rate a freelancer after an assignment?",
            answer:'On the Dashboard, click on the "Archive" icon. There you can search for the relevant freelancer and the assignment he/she has performed. Then click on the name of the freelancer. Then you come to the profile of the Freelancer and there you can easily give a review.'
        },{
            question:"Can you search for freelancers with certain specializations?",
            answer:"Yes! You can select specific specializations via our extensive search system. \n As far as specializations are concerned, childcare organizations can opt for freelancers with different competences. \n For example, you can indicate whether you are looking for pedagogical employees with a VVE certificate, a pedagogical coach, a teaching assistant or a pedagogical employee."
        },{
            question:"I want to hire a freelancer on a permanent basis, is that allowed?",
            answer:"Our General Terms and Conditions stipulate that an organization / company always has the option to hire a freelancer on a permanent basis, if the parties so wish. There are no costs associated with the outflow of a freelancer to permanent employment."
        },{
            question:"How many freelancers use Curant24?",
            answer:"That differs per country because Curant24 is active worldwide, we have 500,000+ freelancers in different industries in our database. Who use Curant24 on a daily basis. \n There is a suitable freelancer for every project."
        }
    ],
    generalChildcare:[
        {
            question:"How does linking freelancers to the Childcare Persons Register work?",
            answer:"Curant24 cannot link freelancers to an organization in the register. Both parties are responsible for this themselves. We do, however, ensure that the correct data of an organization can be found on the portal, in order to make linking as easy as possible for the self-employed. There are also various options for sending reminders from the portal to freelancers for a matching request."
        },{
            question:"Register of Persons (PRK) and submitting a matching request?",
            answer:"In short Everyone who lives or works in a place where children are cared for must register in the Childcare Persons Register (PRK). This is only possible with a valid Certificate of Good Conduct (VOG). Register in 2 steps - The person who is obliged to register must register with a valid VOG.\n  This is done by the person required to register. \n The childcare organization or the childminder agency links the registered person to the organisation. The holder of the childcare must ensure that those people who are required to register are registered and linked. If this is not done in time, the municipality can fine the holder."
        },{
            question:"I cannot find the LRK number of the reception organization or the indicated LRK number seems incorrect.",
            answer:"Go to: https://www.landelijkregisterkinderopvang.nl/pp/#/ Tip: Try to fill in as few fields as possible for a better search result."
        },{
            question:"How to register in the childcare register of persons?",
            answer:"Go to: https://mensenregisterkinderopvang.duo.nl/ \n 1. Log in with your citizen service number and your DigiD Link opens an external page. \n 2. Indicate whether you want to receive messages from the register via the MyGovernment Message Box or by e-mail. \n 3. Enter the reference of your VOG. After your VOG has been approved, you pay € 12 registration costs via iDEAL."
        },{
            question:"I am trying to link to Curant24 in the Register of Persons, but I am unable to",
            answer:"You cannot link to Curant24 because Curant24 is not a childcare organisation. The reason why we ask for a screenshot of your registration in the Register of Persons is so that we can see that you are registered and so we verify your name as a registered person at Curant24."
        },{
            question:"I am registered in the Register of Persons but cannot link me yet..",
            answer:"You cannot link to Curant24 because Curant24 is not a childcare organisation. \n The reason why we ask for a screenshot of your registration in the Register of Persons is so that we can see that you are registered and so we verify your name as a registered person at Curant24. \n With your first assignment as a freelancer, you can link yourself to the relevant client/childcare organisation"
        },{
            question:"How does the childcare register work?",
            answer:"The Childcare Persons Register (PRK) is a system in which everyone who works or lives at an address where children are cared for is registered. People who register in the PRK must have a VOG."
        },{
            question:"Can a freelancer who speaks insufficient Dutch work for us (childcare organisation)?",
            answer:"Pedagogical staff who (want to) work in the VVE must demonstrably master the language level 3F for oral language skills and reading. \n The language level 3F requirement applies from 1 August 2017 for pedagogical staff working in pre-school education in the G37 (large municipalities) and G86 (medium-sized municipalities). \n The requirement will come into effect on 1 August 2019 for pedagogical employees working in pre-school education in the other municipalities. Kinderopvangtotaal indicates the following standard: https://assets.kinderopvang.nl/p/393216/files/Factsheet%20over%20de%20aantoonbaar%2"
        },{
            question:"What is the language requirement 3F?",
            answer:"Good language development is important for the child to make a good start in primary education. A language-rich environment is crucial here. \n Pedagogical staff must therefore have at least level 3F or B2 for oral language skills. An integration model is used for this. The requirements for the minimum language level for professionals will come into effect on January 1, 2025."
        },{
            question:"Can the freelancer privately babysit children that the freelancer knows from childcare?",
            answer:"Each childcare center has its own pedagogical policy, code of conduct and conditions. \n Consult the relevant childcare center with your question. Curant24 is only the mediator and has no position on such issues."
        }
    ]
}

export const freelancerQuestions = {
    general:[
    {
        question:"Is Curant24 an intermediary?",
        answer: "Curant24 is more than just a mediator between organizations / companies and freelancers. We offer: \n - an extensive international and national online platform where we bring supply and demand together.\n - We take over the total administration of both parties\n - An online system (your Curant24 account) where all documents can be found such as contracts, time sheets, invoices, receipts\n"
    },{
        question:"What is Curant24?",
        answer: "Curant24 is a platform where freelancers and clients from every conceivable industry do business with each other.\n Clients have the option to search for freelancers for free in our extensive database for their assignment. Or can immediately call on the help of Curant24. And vice versa, freelancers can search for the most current assignments on Curant24 \n Curant 24 was founded in 2009 and has offices in various countries worldwide. Curant24 is an intermediary agency that brings freelancers from every industry together with clients.\n Curant24 is part of NatureTower bv with more than 100 employees worldwide."
    },{
        question:"How did Curant24 originate?",
        answer:"Curant 24 was founded in 2009 and has offices in various countries worldwide. Curant24 is an intermediary agency that brings freelancers from every industry together with clients.\n  Curant24 is part of NatureTower bv with more than 100 employees worldwide.\n"
    },{
        question:"How does Curant24 work for the freelancer?",
        answer:"On Curant24 you will find various assignments for you as a freelancer. From plumber to childcare. First you create a Curant24 account and then you view the available assignments. Is there anything interesting in there? Then click on 'I am interested' and let the client know that you are interested.\nIs the client also interested in your services?\nThen we discuss all the conditions of the assignment together with the client. So that there are no surprises for both parties. If everything has been properly discussed and both parties agree to the terms and conditions.\nThen Curant24 does the rest and we arrange all administration between both parties.\nYou only need to submit your work hours weekly in your Curant24 account. Your invoice is automatically generated from the system every Tuesday and sent to the client.\nThis is all neatly stored in your account.\nAnd you can choose when you have the invoices paid, 7, 14 or 30 days\n"
    },{
        question:"How does Curant24 work for the client?",
        answer:"On Curant24 you will find various freelancers from plumbers to childcare for your assignments. In just a few clicks you can create an account and post a assignment. You can invite suitable freelancers or freelancers themselves show interest in your assignment.\n Have you found the right freelancer and is the freelancer also interested in your assignment?\n Then we discuss all the conditions of the assignment together with the freelancer. So that there are no surprises for both parties. If everything has been properly discussed and both parties agree to the terms and conditions. Then only the contracts are signed\nThen Curant24 does the rest and we arrange all administration between both parties.\nYou will receive the invoices neatly in your Curant24 account every week. In your account you will also find all contracts between you and the freelancers, invoices, working hours of the freelancers, and any receipts."
    },{
        question:"How do I create a Curant24 account (profile)?",
        answer:"You can sign up for free and without obligation via the www.Curant24.nl platform, via this link"
    },{
        question:"Why freelancers choose Curant24",
        answer:"Curant24 is specialized internationally and nationally and is active in every industry. Thanks to our broad knowledge of the profession, we know better than anyone else what each industry looks like and what the possibilities are.\nBecause of the good cooperation with clients over the years who use our platform to place their assignments. Can we offer you as freelancers a valuable offer?\n"
    },{
        question:"What makes Curant24 different from other agencies.",
        answer:"Various consultants work at Curant24, all of whom have knowledge of their industry. Thanks to our experience, knowledge and close cooperation with companies, organizations and freelancers, we know what is needed within a company or organization to successfully complete a assignment.\n We strive to take a assignment to a higher level by not only looking at the required qualities of the freelancer. But we also look at the person, does the freelancer fit in with the organization or company? We know from experience that a match on paper is not always a match."
    },{
        question:"Why do clients choose Curant24",
        answer:"Most clients like to keep their focus on the core business. It takes time to find a suitable freelancer. That is why clients have been using us since 2009. We are specialists in mediating the right freelancers with clients.\nClients also have the option to search for a freelancer free of charge via our extensive database of freelancers. The advantage of this is that it is clearly indicated which freelancers are immediately available. And we only have qualified and screened freelancers in our database.\nIf a assignment has to be carried out abroad, we also have Curant24 branches that are active abroad. Who could be looking for a freelancer internationally.\n"
    },{
        question:"What does Curant24 do with my personal and company data",
        answer:"View and download the privacy statement here"
    },{
        question:"What about the responsibility in case of incidents during the assignments?",
        answer:"Curant24 is only the mediator and is not liable in the event of incidents during assignments. The freelancer is insured for accidents/incidents during work.\nWithout business liability insurance, the freelancers are not allowed to work via Curant24"
    },{
        question:"Can I recruit people from the company or organizations I work with?",
        answer:"No, that is absolutely not allowed. It is already very difficult for companies and organizations to find and keep suitable personnel. We like it when you bring in new people, but don't try to recruit direct colleagues."
    },{
        question:"Can I keep my mobile phone with me during my assignment?",
        answer:"We cannot answer this question for you. The company or organization you work with determines the rules during the assignment. Most companies/organizations allow you to use your phone during breaks, but your phone is stored in your bag or jacket while working in the group."
    },{
        question:"Does Curant24 also have an app?",
        answer:"Curant has both an Android and an iPhone app"
    },{
        question:"Can you work via Curant24 if you are also employed?",
        answer:"Depending on the agreements you have with your employer, you can be employed and also work as a freelancer."
    },{
        question:"I am already freelancer - do I have to re-register with the Chamber of Commerce?",
        answer:"If you are already freelancer or freelancer, you are already registered with the Chamber of Commerce (KvK). You do not need to re-register to get started at Curant24."
    },{
        question:"For freelancers in childcare: ",
        answer: 'Please note that the target description when registering with the Chamber of Commerce is: "The provision of pedagogical services to childcare centers involving the care, education and contribution to the development of children. All this in accordance with the provisions in Article 1.1. to the Childcare Act SBI code childcare: 88.91 Childcare and playgroup work 88.91.1 Childcare SBI code pedagogues: 86.91.3 Practices of Psychotherapists, Psychologists and Pedagogues"'
    },{
        question:"I am unable to upload my documents to my profile.",
        answer:"You can only upload your documents as PDF. Below is a link to convert your documents into PDF format, if necessary: ​​https://www.google.com/search?client=firefox-b-d&q=jpg+convert+to+pdf"
    },{
        question:"My VOG is no longer valid, what now?",
        answer:"Send us an email with your full name, initials and surname and we can send you a pre-completed VOG application form. You can email your request to: info@curant24.nl"
    },{
        question:"I would like to apply for a VOG, is that possible via Curant24?",
        answer:"Send us an email with your full name, initials and surname and we can send you a pre-completed VOG - application form. You can email your request to: info@curant24.nl"
    },{
        question:"I am already registered with the Chamber of Commerce as an independent entrepreneur. Can I pass on the same Chamber of Commerce number/excerpt?",
        answer:"If you are already freelancer or freelancer, you are already registered with the Chamber of Commerce (KvK). You do not need to re-register to get started at Curant24."
    },{
        question:"Is there work as a coach",
        answer:"Curant24 is not an employer, but we regularly ask senior freelancers to offer novice freelancers support at the very beginning. These coaches also help you to use our platform optimally."
    },{
        question:"I am unable to upload my documents to my profile.",
        answer:"You can only upload your documents as PDF. \n Below is a link to convert your documents into PDF format, if necessary: \n ​​https://www.google.com/search?client=firefox-b-d&q=jpg+convert+to+pdf"
    }
    ],
    invoicesPayments:[
        {
            question:"What do I earn as a self-employed person at Curant24?",
            answer:"You are free to determine your own rate as a self-employed person within Curant24. Most self-employed people at Curant24 charge between 20 and 60 euros per hour."
        },{
            question:"How do I keep track of my hours and send my invoices to the organizations / companies myself?",
            answer:"Curant24 takes over the entire administration for you, all you have to do is upload your signed timesheet every week and any receipts in your Curant24 account.We send the invoices to the organizations / companies on your behalf. Everything is neatly kept in your personal account."
        },{
            question:"Where can I find my old invoice number?",
            answer:"You have to enter the invoice number yourself on the invoice after you have downloaded it. This is because by law invoice numbers must always be consecutive. \n We have no insight into the invoices that you may send to clients who are not affiliated with Curant24. \n An invoice number must also be unique. You are not allowed to send an invoice twice with the same number."
        },{
            question:"What are my travel costs and are they reimbursed?",
            answer:"Travel expenses are not reimbursed by all companies / organizations. You can always deduct this from your tax."
        },{
            question:"Do I invoice Curant24 as a freelancer? Think point",
            answer:"No, we send the invoices for you to the clients and they then pay you. This is neatly kept in your account. As soon as an invoice has been paid, it will immediately be visible in your account. \n All you have to do is upload your signed timesheet every week and any receipts in your Curant24 account. \n We closely monitor whether the invoices are paid on time by the organizations / companies. Nothing is more annoying than having to wait for your money. \n You can also find all sent invoices in your Curant24 account "
        },{
            question:"Can I send my invoice daily, weekly or monthly?",
            answer:"Situation-oriented long-term work or short \n As a self-employed person, you are an entrepreneur, so that means that you determine how often you invoice in consultation with your client. Most opt ​​for monthly invoicing. You can invoice via the platform, but you are of course also free to send your own invoice. The invoices are only available when the period has ended! So the weekly invoices are prepared on Saturday and the monthly invoices on the first day of the following month. Most clients want an invoice per month, which saves a lot of administrative work. \n Send an invoice every week, more clear \n "
        },{
            question:"How do I register my hours?",
            answer:"Curant24 takes over the entire administration for you, all you have to do is upload your signed timesheet every week and any receipts in your Curant24 account."
        },{
            question:"Who do I contact for my accounting?",
            answer:"In your Curant24 account, your entire bookkeeping is neatly maintained for the clients for whom you work via Curant24."
        },{
            question:"How do I get paid as a self-employed person?",
            answer:"As a freelancer, you can view your invoices for each week in Curant24, showing how many hours you have worked and for what rate. \n We send the invoices for you to the clients and they then pay you. This is neatly kept in your account. As soon as an invoice has been paid, it will immediately be visible in your account. \nWe closely monitor whether the invoices are paid on time by the organizations / companies. Nothing is more annoying than having to wait for your money. \n"
        },{
            question:"Where can I find my (old) invoices?",
            answer:"All invoices are neatly stored in your Curant24 account, you can directly download every invoice from every period and use it for your own administration. \n You can search invoices by date via our extensive search engine."
        },{
            question:"How is the hourly rate determined?",
            answer:"Freelancers are independent entrepreneurs and set their own hourly rate. \nThe hourly rate is indicated on the profile of the PM and includes all costs, such as travel costs, parking costs, etc. We have chosen to state the rates including any VAT. \n The reason for this is that childcare as a sector is exempt from VAT. After all, clients cannot set off any VAT. \n A large number of freelancers are exempt from VAT, either because they make use of the Small Businesses Scheme (KOR) or because the tax authorities have decided that they are exempt."
        },{
            question:"Are there any costs involved?",
            answer:"No, no extra arrivals will be charged to the freelancer"
        },{
            question:"I have not yet received a VAT number, can I already accept and carry out assignments?",
            answer:"Yes, you can already accept and carry out assignments, but you cannot yet send invoices because the VAT number is legally required on an invoice to another entrepreneur (clients, reception organisations)."
        }
    ],
    cancellations:[
        {
            question:"The freelancer is already on location and working, but I will no longer need the freelancer. Can I still shorten the service?",
            answer:"When a service has started, a change is limited. A shift for a day, for example 8 or 9 hours, can be shortened by 1 hour in case of redundancy. The reason for this is that the Tadaah has reserved this day for work and an agreement has been made for this. Afternoon or morning shifts, for example BSO (out-of-school care), cannot be shortened."
        },{
            question:"Can I cancel a freelancer if a freelancer is already scheduled?",
            answer:"The assignment agreement states that a service can always be canceled free of charge up to 24 hours before the start. A cancellation within 24 hours before the start is also possible, but the contractor will then receive a compensation of € 100,= for lost income, only if he cannot get a replacement assignment for the day in question."
        },{
            question:"The freelancer is redundant and has indicated that he will not complete the scheduled service in full. How can we still adjust the service?",
            answer:"If the freelancer and the organization or company have jointly agreed to adjust / shorten the planned service after the start, this change must be recorded in writing. An assignment agreement has been entered into and this can only be changed if both parties agree. A change must be communicated to info@curant24"
        },{
            question:"I have an assignment agreement with a freelancer that I want to change, is that possible?",
            answer:"Yes that is possible, the terms and conditions and the assignment agreement state that a client, in all reasonableness, requires a freelancer to carry out the assignment at a different location. \n The following must be taken into account: if the client wishes such a change, the associated costs (travel costs, parking costs and travel time) will be borne by the client. After all, it is the client who wants the change.\n  For example, a freelancer is hired at a location with free parking for a 9am-5pm shift. The client wants this person to go to another location where parking has been paid, then the costs of parking are for the client. \n The costs for traveling there and the travel time (in accordance with the hourly rate) are also for the account of the client. If the freelancer uses the car, it is reasonable to charge € 0.19 per kilometer. If public transport is used, the travel costs can easily be determined using the OV chip card or the travel costs according to the website 9292.nl."
        },{
            question:"A situation has arisen where the use of the freelancer is no longer necessary, what are the options?",
            answer:"That depends on whether the service has already started. A service has commenced after the expiry of the date and time as stated in the assignment agreement. The assignment can then no longer be withdrawn, it is possible to shorten the assignment by a maximum of 1 hour, an assignment of 9 hours can be shortened to 8 hours. \n This may, for example, be used in the event of redundancy or any other circumstance as a result of which the client is forced to close a project, including corona-related measures. \n The assignment can be canceled up to 24 hours before the start of the service, in which case the client owes the contractor a fee of € 100. \n If the assignment is canceled earlier, so before 24 hours before the start, there are no costs involved."
        },{
            question:"My child is sick and I don't have a babysitter? What now? Can I still cancel my order?",
            answer:"Accepted assignments can be canceled 24 hours before the start of the assignment (day). After that, you can only call in sick in emergencies such as illness or a death in family. Sick calls are only accepted with a valid reason. You must report sick to Curant24 and also to the client. There are a number of freelancers on reserve from Curant24, the service will also be available again for your colleagues"
        },{
            question:"What if I am ill or unable to carry out the assignment?",
            answer:"When you have accepted a service, you have entered into an agreement to work. You have made a regular appointment. You can't just cancel it. In emergency situations or force majeure, you can call in sick. In the event of illness, you must inform both the client and Curant24 to report sick with a valid reason."
        },{
            question:"I have accepted an assignment but cannot execute it. What should I do now?",
            answer:"From now on, both the contractor (freelancer) and the client can cancel an assignment free of charge up to 24 hours before the start."
        }
    ],
    generalChildcare:[
        {
            question:"How does linking freelancers to the Childcare Persons Register work?",
            answer:"Curant24 cannot link freelancers to an organization in the register. Both parties are responsible for this themselves. We do, however, ensure that the correct data of an organization can be found on the portal, in order to make linking as easy as possible for the self-employed. There are also various options for sending reminders from the portal to freelancers for a matching request."
        },{
            question:"Register of Persons (PRK) and submitting a matching request.",
            answer:"Information: \n In short Everyone who lives or works in a place where children are cared for must register in the Childcare Persons Register (PRK). \n This is only possible with a valid Certificate of Good Conduct (VOG). Register in 2 steps - The person who is obliged to register must register with a valid VOG. This is done by the person required to register. -The childcare organization or the childminder agency links the registered person to the organisation. \n The holder of the childcare must ensure that those people who are required to register are registered and linked. If this is not done in time, the municipality can fine the holder."
        },{
            question:"I cannot find the LRK number of the reception organization or the indicated LRK number seems incorrect.",
            answer:"Go to: https://www.landelijkregisterkinderopvang.nl/pp/#/ Tip: Try to fill in as few fields as possible for a better search result"
        },{
            question:"How to register in the childcare register of persons?",
            answer:"Go to: https://mensenregisterkinderopvang.duo.nl/ 1. Log in with your citizen service number and your DigiD Link opens an external page. 2. Indicate whether you want to receive messages from the register via the MyGovernment Message Box or by e-mail. 3. Enter the reference of your VOG. After your VOG has been approved, you pay € 12 registration costs via iDEAL."
        },{
            question:"I am trying to link to Curant24 in the Register of Persons, but I am unable to",
            answer:"You cannot link to Curant24 because Curant24 is not a childcare organisation. The reason why we ask for a screenshot of your registration in the Register of Persons is so that we can see that you are registered and so we verify your name as a registered person at Curant24."
        },{
            question:"I am registered in the Register of Persons but cannot link me yet.",
            answer:"You cannot link to Curant24 because Curant24 is not a childcare organisation. The reason why we ask for a screenshot of your registration in the Register of Persons is so that we can see that you are registered and so we verify your name as a registered person at Curant24. \n With your first assignment as a freelancer, you can link yourself to the relevant client/childcare organisation.,☻"
        },{
            question:"How does the childcare register work?",
            answer:"The Childcare Persons Register (PRK) is a system in which everyone who works or lives at an address where children are cared for is registered. People who register in the PRK must have a VOG."
        },{
            question:"Can a freelancer who speaks insufficient Dutch work for us (childcare organisation)?",
            answer:"Pedagogical staff who (want to) work in the VVE must demonstrably master the language level 3F for oral language skills and reading. \n The language level 3F requirement applies from 1 August 2017 for pedagogical staff working in pre-school education in the G37 (large municipalities) and G86 (medium-sized municipalities). \n The requirement will come into effect on 1 August 2019 for pedagogical employees working in pre-school education in the other municipalities. Kinderopvangtotaal indicates the following standard: https://assets.kinderopvang.nl/p/393216/files/Factsheet%20over%20de%20aantoonbaar%2"
        },{
            question:"What is the language requirement 3F?",
            answer:"Good language development is important for the child to make a good start in primary education. A language-rich environment is crucial here. Pedagogical staff must therefore have at least level 3F or B2 for oral language skills. An integration model is used for this. The requirements for the minimum language level for professionals will come into effect on January 1, 2025."
        },{
            question:"Register of Persons (PRK) and submission of a matching request.",
            answer:"Information: \n In short Everyone who lives or works in a place where children are cared for must register in the Childcare Persons Register (PRK). \n This is only possible with a valid Certificate of Good Conduct (VOG). Register in 2 steps - The person who is obliged to register must register with a valid VOG. This is done by the person required to register. \n -The childcare organization or the childminder agency links the registered person to the organisation. \n The holder of the childcare must ensure that those people who are required to register are registered and linked. \n If this is not done in time, the municipality can fine the holder"
        },{
            question:"Can I babysit privately for children I know from childcare?",
            answer:"Each childcare center has its own pedagogical policy, code of conduct and conditions. Consult the relevant childcare center with your question. Curant24 is only the mediator and has no position on such issues."
        },{
            question:"With which HBO study are you allowed to work during the BSO training?",
            answer:"These are a number of studies with which you can work at the BSO if you have obtained 50% of your credits. In case of doubt, look here: https://www.kinderopvang-werkt.nl/veelvragen/opleidingen-qualification-eis-pedagogisch-werker/welk-diploma \n Primary education teacher (at Hogeschool, PABO or IPABO) Pedagogy (HBO bachelor) Social Pedagogical Assistance (SPH) Cultural and Social Education (CMV) Pedagogical management Childcare Associate Degree Pedagogical Educational Employee Associate Degree Childcare Associate Degree Educational Supporter Social Studies Associate Degree Pedagogical Professional Child and Education."
        }
    ],
    freelance:[
        {
            question:"How do I become self-employed or self-employed?",
            answer:'To become self-employed or self-employed, you must register yourself with the Chamber of Commerce. You can fill in the details online at www.kvk.nl and then make an appointment to complete the registration. \n Or click on the link: https://www.kvk.nl/inschrijven-en-wijzigen/inschrijven-onderneming-eenmanszaak/ \nWorking in childcare. !!!!!! \nPurpose description when registering with the Chamber of Commerce: "Providing pedagogical services to childcare centers involving the care, education and contribution to the development of children. \n All this in accordance with the provisions of Article 1.1. of the Childcare Act."'
        },{
            question:"I have found an organization / company via Curant24 and I want to be employed there. What now?",
            answer:"Congratulations, it's great that you have found an organization / company where you can get started. According to our Terms and Conditions, the organization / company and you must submit a request in writing. There are no costs involved. Outflow of freelancers to permanent employment is free."
        },{
            question:"Can you work via Curant24 if you are also employed?",
            answer:"Depending on the agreements you have with your employer, you can be employed and also work as a freelancer via Curant24."
        },{
            question:"Will I receive an evaluation and/or a performance interview at Curant24?",
            answer:"We at Tadaah do not judge you on your performance. The organizations with whom you have carried out assignments are given the opportunity to assess you.  \n Good reviews will give you a star on your profile. You can receive a maximum of 5 stars per assignment. The average of all stars is displayed on your profile. That is good to know for future clients."
        },{
            question:"I have just expressed interest in an assignment. Will I get a message about that?",
            answer:"You will only receive a message if you are the one who has chosen the organization or company for the assignment. Curant24 does not assign freelancers to an assignment. \n The organization / company determines the assignment itself and also chooses who may complete the assignment. We also assess the chosen freelancer, of course, but the organization / company ultimately has the last word.\n Curant24 cannot provide you with information about the status of the order."
        },{
            question:"I have an assignment agreement with an organization but I want to be replaced, is that possible and how does this work?",
            answer:"A freelancer is not an employee and therefore different provisions apply. Three elements are met in an employment contract: \n (1) there is a relationship of authority, \n (2) wages are paid and \n (3) there is an obligation to perform the work personally. \n An assignment agreement is not an employment contract because there is no obligation to perform the work personally. \n It is therefore possible that a freelancer is replaced by another. However, it is only possible if the replacement meets the same objective criteria to be allowed to perform this service. \n By this we mean: having a correct VOG, a correct diploma and professional liability insurance. \n Watch out for freelancers in childcare.It is important to take into account that the responsible employee of the childcare organization ensures that the VOG is linked in the Childcare Persons Register, that the diploma is checked for authenticity and whether it is suitable for the assignment that is being carried out. \n The freelancer who is the contractor (according to the assignment agreement) remains responsible for the execution of the assignment, as well as for entering the weekly working hours in the Curant24 account."
        },{
            question:"I have an assignment agreement with a client who wants to change it, is that possible?",
            answer:"Yes that is possible, the terms and conditions and the assignment agreement state that a client, in all reasonableness, requires a freelancer to carry out the assignment at a different location. \n The following must be taken into account: if the client wishes such a change, the associated costs (travel costs, parking costs and travel time) will be borne by the client. After all, it is the client who wants the change. For example, a freelancer is hired at a location with free parking for a 9am-5pm shift. The client wants this person to go to another location where parking has been paid, then the costs of parking are for the client. \n The costs for traveling there and the travel time (in accordance with the hourly rate) are also for the account of the client. If a freelancer uses the car, it is reasonable to charge € 0.19 per kilometer. \n If public transport is used, the travel costs can easily be determined using the OV chip card or the travel costs according to the website 9292.nl."
        },{
            question:"Where can I find my (old) invoices?",
            answer:"All invoices are always neatly stored in your Curant24 account by Curant24. You can see everything in your account, such as agreements per client, invoices, time sheets and any receipts."
        },{
            question:"Where can I find my old invoice number?",
            answer:"You have to enter the invoice number yourself on the invoice after you have downloaded it. This is because by law invoice numbers must always be consecutive. We have no insight into the invoices that you may send to clients who are not affiliated with Curant24. An invoice number must also be unique. You are not allowed to send an invoice twice with the same number"
        },{
            question:"What conditions must I meet as a freelancer?",
            answer:'You can find the conditions on the website of kvk.nl and tax authorities.nl. There are also videos from Chamber of Commerce on Youtube where this is explained. Link: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLbE4XGSrywI3WmmjX7GyuielWPMj_ZOZM \n Working in childcare Purpose description when registering with the Chamber of Commerce: "Providing pedagogical services to childcare centers involving the care, education and contribution to the development of children. All this in accordance with the provisions of Article 1.1. of the Childcare Act."'
        },{
            question:"I am already self-employed - do I have to re-register with the Chamber of Commerce?",
            answer:'If you are already self-employed or self-employed, you are already registered with the Chamber of Commerce (KvK). You do not need to re-register to get started at Curant24. \n For freelancers who work in childcare. Please note that the target description when registering with the Chamber of Commerce is: "The provision of pedagogical services to childcare centers involving the care, education and contribution to the development of children.\n All this in accordance with the provisions in Article 1.1. to the Childcare Act SBI code childcare: 88.91 Childcare and playgroup work 88.91.1 Childcare SBI code pedagogues: 86.91.3 Practices of Psychotherapists, Psychologists and Pedagogues'
        },{
            question:"Is an extract from the registration of the Chamber of Commerce required to apply for business liability insurance?",
            answer:"Yes, it is mandatory."
        },{
            question:"Do I need to apply for business liability insurance?",
            answer:"Yes, that is mandatory to work for our organizations / companies via Curant24."
        }
    ],
    qualifications:[
        {
            question:"I don't speak enough Dutch. So can I join in?",
            answer:"Pedagogical staff who (want to) work in the VVE must demonstrably master the language level 3F for oral language skills and reading. \n The language level 3F requirement applies from 1 August 2017 for pedagogical staff working in pre-school education in the G37 (large municipalities) and G86 (medium-sized municipalities). \n The requirement will come into effect on 1 August 2019 for pedagogical employees working in pre-school education in the other municipalities. \n Kinderopvangtotaal indicates the following standard: https://assets.kinderopvang.nl/p/393216/files/Factsheet%20over%20de%20aantoonbaar%2"
        },{
            question:"What is the language requirement 3F?",
            answer:"Good language development is important for the child to make a good start in primary education. A language-rich environment is crucial here. Pedagogical staff must therefore have at least level 3F or B2 for oral language skills. An integration model is used for this. The requirements for the minimum language level for professionals will come into effect on January 1, 2025."
        },{
            question:"Which diploma do I need to work via Curant24?",
            answer:"To be able to work through Curant24 you need a valid diploma to work in childcare. The list of diplomas that allows you to work in childcare is regulated by the government. If you become a member of Curant24, we will check whether your diploma is valid for this. You can also check it yourself on the website https://www.kinderopvang-werkt.nl/check-mijn-diploma."
        },{
            question:"How does the Certificate of Good Conduct (VOG) work?",
            answer:"In the past, each client, ie each childcare center where a substitute worked, required a separate statement of behaviour. Since 1 March 2018, continuous screening via the register of persons has also been active for temporary workers, which makes it easier for the self-employed. A certificate of good conduct only needs to be requested once, after registration in the register of persons, the pedagogical employee can then start working for all clients!"
        },{
            question:"Do you have internships at Curant24?",
            answer:"We are a recognized internship training company and have a number of internships at Curant24 (in the field of administration, social media, marketing) available at the office. However, we are currently unable to offer internships at organizations / companies."
        },{
            question:"I am a HBO student, can I work in childcare via Curant24?",
            answer:"To be able to work via Curant24 you need a valid diploma to be able to work in childcare. \n 4th year HBO students who have obtained 75% of their credits are already allowed to work in childcare. From 1 February 2021 this is 50% of the credits. The list of studies and diplomas that allow you to work in childcare is regulated by the government. \n If you become a member of Curant24, we will check whether your diploma is valid for this. \n You can also check it yourself on the website https://www.kinderopvang-werkt.nl/check-mijn-diploma. This does not apply to MBO students."
        },{
            question:"Do you have to link yourself to the organization you will be working with in the register of persons?",
            answer:"Before you start an assignment, you must be linked to the register of persons, otherwise you will not be able to work. Make sure you send a matching request yourself or contact us so that the organization can match you."
        },{
            question:"I am an MBO student, can I already work in childcare via Curant24?",
            answer:"No, you can't until you graduate. You may only work at your internship during your training."
        },{
            question:"I have a foreign diploma. Can I work via Curant24?",
            answer:"If you want to work in the Netherlands with a foreign diploma, first check what you need to do to have your diploma recognized in the Netherlands. Visit Nuffic.nl: https://www.nuffic.nl/onderwerpen/jouw-buitenlandse-diploma-in-Nederland/"
        },{
            question:"I am a lateral entrant and would like to accept assignments via Curant24, is that allowed?",
            answer:"To be able to work via Curant24 you need a valid diploma to be able to work in childcare. The list of diplomas that allows you to work in childcare is regulated by the government. If you become a member of Curant24, we will check whether your diploma is valid for this. You can also check it yourself on the website https://www.kinderopvang-werkt.nl/check-mijn-diploma."
        },{
            question:"With which HBO study are you allowed to work during the BSO training?",
            answer:"These are a number of studies with which you can work at the BSO if you have obtained 50% of your credits. In case of doubt, look here: https://www.kinderopvang-werkt.nl/veelvragen/opleidingen-qualification-eis-pedagogisch-werker/welk-diploma Primary education teacher (at Hogeschool, PABO or IPABO) Pedagogy (HBO bachelor) Social Pedagogical Assistance (SPH) Cultural and Social Education (CMV) Pedagogical management Childcare Associate Degree Pedagogical Educational Employee Associate Degree Childcare Associate Degree Educational Supporter Social Studies Associate Degree Pedagogical Professional Child and Education."
        }
    ],
    education:[
        {
            question:"Are there career opportunities at Curant24?",
            answer:"A freelancer is not an employee and that is why there are no career opportunities at Curant24. Curant24 is not an employer but only a mediator between organizations / companies and freelancers. If you grow through training and courses, for example as a pedagogical coach or by offering workshops, you can of course use this for clients."
        },{
            question:"I have experience in childcare, but my diploma no longer qualifies?",
            answer:"If you have previous experience in childcare or working with children, but your diploma no longer qualifies, then an EVC program may be a good option. An EVC trajectory means a shortened training, in which your previous experience is taken into account, so you can get started quickly! https://www.evc-centrum-nederland.nl/van-experience-in-de-kinderopvang-naar-geldig-diploma"
        },{
            question:"What is the language requirement 3F?",
            answer:"Good language development is important for the child to make a good start in primary education. A language-rich environment is crucial here. Pedagogical staff must therefore have at least level 3F or B2 for oral language skills. An integration model is used for this. The requirements for the minimum language level for professionals will come into effect on January 1, 2025."
        },{
            question:"With which HBO study are you allowed to work during the BSO training?",
            answer:"These are a number of studies with which you can work at the BSO if you have obtained 50% of your credits. In case of doubt, look here: https://www.kinderopvang-werkt.nl/veelvragen/opleidingen-qualification-eis-pedagogisch-werker/welk-diploma Primary education teacher (at Hogeschool, PABO or IPABO) Pedagogy (HBO bachelor) Social Pedagogical Assistance (SPH) Cultural and Social Education (CMV) Pedagogical management Childcare Associate Degree Pedagogical Educational Employee Associate Degree Childcare Associate Degree Educational Supporter Social Studies Associate Degree Pedagogical Professional Child and Education."
        },{
            question:"With which HBO study are you allowed to work during the BSO training?",
            answer:"These are a number of studies with which you can work at the BSO if you have obtained 50% of your credits. In case of doubt, look here: https://www.kinderopvang-werkt.nl/veelvragen/opleidingen-qualification-eis-pedagogisch-werker/welk-diploma \n Primary education teacher (at Hogeschool, PABO or IPABO) Pedagogy (HBO bachelor) Social Pedagogical Assistance (SPH) Cultural and Social Education (CMV) Pedagogical management Childcare Associate Degree Pedagogical Educational Employee Associate Degree Childcare Associate Degree Educational Supporter Social Studies Associate Degree Pedagogical Professional Child and Education."
        }
    ],
    assignments:[
        {
            question:"Can I also accept orders directly from Curant24's clients, outside of Curant24?",
            answer:"No, this is not allowed. Clients remain customers of Curant24 at all times. Clients of Curant24 are not allowed to directly offer assignments to the freelancers and vice versa. This is in conflict with the General Terms and Conditions of Curant24. See our Terms and Conditions."
        },{
            question:"What about the responsibility in case of incidents during the assignments?",
            answer:"Curant24 is only the mediator and is not liable in the event of incidents during assignments. As a freelancer you are insured for accidents/incidents during work, but it is useful to first discuss what the policy of the organization / company says."
        },{
            question:"Can I execute/accept multiple assignments per day?",
            answer:"You can accept multiple assignments per day on the platform, provided the hours do not overlap."
        },{
            question:"Am I being assessed and where can I see this?",
            answer:"Curant24 does not assess your performance. The organizations / companies with whom you have carried out assignments are given the opportunity to assess you. Good reviews will give you a star on your profile. You can receive a maximum of 5 stars per assignment. The average of all stars is displayed on your profile. That is good to know for future clients."
        },{
            question:"A situation has arisen where the deployment of the freelancer is no longer necessary, what are the options?",
            answer:"That depends on whether the service has already started. A service has commenced after the expiry of the date and time as stated in the assignment agreement.\n  The assignment can then no longer be withdrawn, it is possible to shorten the assignment by a maximum of 1 hour, an assignment of 9 hours can be shortened to 8 hours. \n This may be used, for example, in the event of redundancy or another circumstance as a result of which the client is forced to close a group, including corona-related measures. \n The assignment can be canceled up to 24 hours before the start of the service, in which case the client owes the contractor a fee of € 100. If the assignment is canceled earlier, so before 24 hours before the start, there are no costs involved."
        },{
            question:"Are there enough assignments within my competences?",
            answer:"Curant24 is active in every industry, thanks to our many contacts with different clients. We always have enough assignments in every competence."
        },{
            question:"What are the reserve services?",
            answer:"Reserve duty, means that you are on standby and go instead of a sick colleague. You will receive an email as soon as a colleague calls in sick, stating which shift you are taking over. That could be the night before or that morning. We ensure that you have a service anyway, so if necessary we will find something for you. You will receive a bonus of 20 euros from us for being available."
        },{
            question:"Will I receive an evaluation and/or a performance interview at Curant24?",
            answer:"We at Curant24 do not assess you on your performance. The organizations with whom you have carried out assignments are given the opportunity to assess you. Good reviews will give you a star on your profile. You can receive a maximum of 5 stars per assignment. The average of all stars is displayed on your profile. That is good to know for future clients."
        }
    ]

};